《行尸走肉》前情提要
Previously, on AMC's "The Walking Dead".
起來  我們救你出去
Get up. We're breaking you out.
我不跟你們走
I'm not going with you.
你命不該絕
It's not your time.
有人為他開門了
Somebody opened the door for him.
我們決定不管怎么樣  都要保護好自己
We decided to protect ourselves no matter what.
我們會一直躲在這里  一直活下去
We would stay hidden, and we would stay alive.
塔拉  你在外面比我們走得都遠
Tara, you've been out further than any of us.
至少你能告訴我們別去哪找
At least you can tell us where not to look.
當然可以
Yeah, sure thing.
她們有槍
They -- They have guns.
許多槍
A lot of them.
我看見了
I saw it.
什么
What?
那個團體
That group.
我遇見的女人們
Um, the women I met.
她們有武器庫  有槍
They have an armory. They have guns.
你之前怎么不跟我們說
Why didn't you tell us before now?
我做過保證  瑞克
I made a promise, Rick.
你會想起你殺掉的人嗎
Do you ever think about who you've killed?
會
Yeah.
如果計劃失敗  你有心理準備嗎
Are you ready if this goes south?
不會失敗的
It won't.
如果失敗了  你不必內疚
If it does, you don't need to feel bad.
我的確內疚
I do feel bad.
我會內疚的
I will.
塔拉
Tara...
你不必
you don't have to.
行尸走肉
『第七季  第十五集』
你得用一塊防水布蓋住
You need ?to cover this with a tarp.
-防水布嗎  -對
- A tarp? ?- Tarp.
為什么
Why?
你想想
Think about it.
直接告訴我吧
Okay. Just tell me.
我們需要保溫
We want warmth
這樣它們就會在冬天來臨之前發芽
so they'll put out shoots before the last freeze.
那樣的話  我們扯掉防水布
That way, we pull back the tarp,
它們就會自然枯亡
they die naturally,
就不用一直除草了
saves on all the endless weeding.
去蓋防水布吧
Get to tarping.
沒問題  女老大
You got it, boss lady.
等等  你去哪
Uh, wait. Where are you going?
我不是農民
I, uh -- I'm not a farmer.
我需要幫助
I need some help here.
你不需要
No, you don't.
我看見外面長著野生藍莓灌木叢
I saw a wild blueberry bush growing outside.
如果足夠嫩
If it's young enough,
我就要把它拔出來  種在這里
I'm gonna pull it up and replant it here.
好植株能結40多年的藍莓
Good one will produce for over 40 years.
我們得開始規劃活那么久了
We got to start acting like we'll be around that long.
挺好的
Cool. Yeah.
就蓋防水布  別碰
Just tarp. Don't touch.
之后我來看看你做得怎么樣
I'll see how you do after.
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
最新連載海外影視劇下載
請登陸 www.YYeTs.com
僅供交流學習  禁止商用盈利
m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1
m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1
翻譯     冰藍 Reginamoon CS小明漫畫家
翻譯     小僵僵 蘑菇 送小孩
你上去后  注意信號
Once you're up, watch for the signal.
幾點開始
What time does the clock start?
校對     送小孩
等她一進去就開始
Soon as she's in.
時間軸     某雪  加森  濤濤
你沒事吧
You good?
后期     送小哥  拉圖
我很好
I'm good enough.
總監     送小孩
很高興你來了  我知道這很難
I'm glad you came. I know it's been hard.
-我知道你不想這樣  -我之前不想
- I know you don't want this. - Didn't want this,
但我現在開始明白是怎么回事了
but I'm starting to understand what's on the menu now.
我們可以像這些人一樣躲藏
We can hide like these people,
我們可以繼續供奉救世軍
we can keep trying to serve The Saviors,
我可以時常看見你被毒打
and I can watch you get randomly beaten every so often,
或者我們可以反抗
or else we can fight.
所以我們來了
So, here we are.
而且跟你在一起
And being with you, well...
讓無助的恐懼可以容忍了
it makes abject terror tolerable.
我該更努力地阻止羅西塔和薩沙的
I should've tried harder to stop Rosita and Sasha.
如果她們再等一天...
If they'd have just waited one more day...
薩沙槍法很好
Well, Sasha's a good shot,
羅西塔知道如何照顧自己
and Rosita knows how to take care of herself.
她們也許現在都回山頂寨了
Probably back at Hilltop right now.
至少我希望如此  我們需要她們
Least I hope so. We're gonna need 'em.
還得死很多人的
There's a whole lot of people still got to die.
你好啊
Hey, there.
沒事吧
You okay?
能給我點水嗎
Can I get some water?
我該自我介紹一下
I should introduce myself.
我是大衛
I'm David.
不知道你昨晚是否記得我
I wonder if you remember me from last night.
你記得嗎
Do you?
不記得
No.
我能原諒你
Well, I can forgive that.
昨晚簡直一團亂
Last night was kind of a shitstorm.
就是我把繩子遞給那些人  把你綁起來的
I was the guy that gave the rope to the guys that tied you up.
我總是帶著一些繩子
I always keep some close.
用繩子能做許多有趣的事情
There's just all kinds of fun and interesting things you can do with rope.
天啊  你真漂亮
God, you're pretty.
如果我給你水喝
If I give you some water,
這是我不該做的事
which is not something I'm supposed to do,
你愿意為我做點事嗎
will you do something for me?
做點你不該做的事
Something you're not supposed to do?
你愿意嗎
Will you?
告訴我你有多渴
Tell me how thirsty you are.
去死吧
Go to hell.
該死
Oh, shit.
反抗只會讓過程更持久
Fighting's just gonna make it last longer.
告訴你  我無所謂
Which, for the record, is fine by me.
大衛
?David!
你他媽在這里干什么呢
What the hell are you doing in here?
尼根  先生
Negan, sir --
你真覺得我需要你回答嗎
Do you really think I need you to answer that?
我能看出你想強奸這女人
I can see that you're trying to rape this woman.
你想強奸這女人  對吧
You were trying to rape this woman, weren't you?
這是不可接受的行為
This is some unacceptable behavior.
強奸違反了這里的規定
Rape is against the rules here.
我可不想待在允許強奸的地方
I wouldn't wanna be somewhere where it wasn't.
負責的人放過這種事...
Someone in charge who let something like that fly...
大衛
David.
你真的越線了
You really crossed a line here.
抱歉  先生
I'm sorry, sir.
知道嗎
You know what?
我不接受你的道歉
I do not accept your apology.
給...
Get, uh...
薩沙
Sasha.
名字真好聽
That is a beautiful name.
給薩沙拿件新襯衫
Get Sasha here a new T-shirt.
很抱歉讓你看到了這些
I'm sorry you had to see that.
繩子的事我也很抱歉
Sorry 'bout the rope, too.
也許有些小題大做
Probably overkill,
但你昨晚鬧了好大一場事
but you did cause one hell of a fracas last night.
該死
Oh, shit.
我記得你
I remember you.
嗯
Yeah.
你當時在場
You were there.
該死  我現在懂了
Oh, hell. I get it now.
我得承認
I got to hand it to you.
你這娘們真他媽有種
You've got some beach-ball-sized lady nuts on you,
不顧死活地就沖進來了
coming in all kamikaze like that.
問題是
Big question here,
我需要你說實話
and I need the truth on this one --
是瑞克派你來的嗎
Did Rick put you up to this?
瑞克
Rick?
你的狗嗎
Your bitch?
不是
No.
不管怎樣  你肯定以為你必死無疑
Either way, you must've thought it was gonna be the end,
畢竟你那樣獨自闖進來
coming in on your lonesome like that.
但事情不會這樣發展
But that's not the way it's got to go.
恰恰相反
Unh-unh. Just the opposite.
這
See, this...
這可能只是個開始
Well, this could be the beginning.
刀現在歸你了
This knife is yours now.
你可以試著使用  干掉我
You can try to use it, take me out,
但考慮到我站在你上方
but considering I am standing above you,
拿著一根球棒
holding a baseball bat,
那可不是明智之舉
that doesn't seem real smart.
你可以用刀來割腕
Now, you can use it to slit your wrists,
這就太可惜了  但我懂
which would be a damn shame, but I get it.
考慮到最近發生的事  你顯然
You're obviously not on the shiny side of the street,
不是什么陽光女人
given recent events.
你可以坐在那里  什么也不做
Now, you can sit there and do nothin',
等著老大衛復活  咬掉你的臉
wait for ol' David to come back to life and eat your face,
這也很可惜  有些瘋狂
also a damn shame and kinda nuts,
但你有權做出選擇
but, hell, to each their own.
或者你可以用刀來干掉強奸犯老大衛
Or you can use that blade and stop ol' Rapey David
阻止他變成強奸犯行尸大衛
from becoming Dead-Alive Rapey David,
自己救自己  加入救世軍
save yourself, join the cause.
我知道我要拿你怎么辦
I know what I'd do.
怎么辦
What?
我少了個男丁
I'm a man short.
媽的  這個人渣算不上男人
Hell, you can't really call this piece of shit a man,
但依然  我少了人
but still, I'm short,
而你這娘們有種極了
and you got those beach-ball-sized lady nuts,
我想要好好利用你的勇氣
and I wanna harness the heat comin' off of 'em.
有朝一日你可以幫我管理這個地方
You can help me run this place one day,
我們所有人一起  跟著規矩走
all of us together, following the rules,
站在同一戰線
workin' on the same side of things.
從來都是這么回事
That's all this was ever about.
你依然可以選這條路
And it still can be for you.
考慮到我的所作所為
I know it's hard to picture,
我知道這有點難以想象
considering what I did.
但是  薩沙  人人都有必須邁過去的坎
But, Sasha, we all got shit to get over.
花點時間  好好想想
Take some time. Think about it.
無論你的決定如何  都由你說了算
Whatever you decide, so it shall be.
別有壓力
No pressure.
還有  再次道歉  很抱歉你不得不目睹那幕
And, again, I am sorry you had to see that,
雖然我知道你是見過場面的
even though I know you have seen some things.
我只希望你能明白...
I just want you to understand...
我們不是怪物
we are not monsters.
他們把你怎么了
What did they do to you?
他們在保護我
They're keepin' me safe.
我給你帶了些能讓你舒服點的東西
I brought you some creature comforts.
實話說  這枕頭不防過敏
Full disclosure, the pillow is not hypoallergenic.
關于我該不該過來有過一些爭論
There was some debate as to whether or not I should come in here.
他們說假如我被你攜刀劫持的話
They said in the event of a hostage situation with the pig sticker
我就只能靠自己了
that I would fully be on my own.
我就這么一說
Just wanted to share that.
尼根向我傳達了他對你的招安之意
Negan relayed to me his offer to you.
在我看來你應該接受
It's my opinion that you should accept said offer,
就像我一樣
just as I did.
我知道這是不得已而為之
I know it's a hold-your-nose situation,
但與這里的頭頭做朋友
but taking up with the management here
真的是正確的選擇
was indeed the correct select.
我曾經認為自己可以勇敢起來
You know, I believed I could be brave,
當一個亞伯拉罕那樣的生存者...
that I could be a survivor like Abraham was,and ...
開著那輛房車駛向夕陽是...
ridin' that RV into the sunset was...
我一生中最棒的37分鐘
some of the greatest 37 minutes of my existence.
但我如今明白那只是一個完全不切實際的幻想
But I know now that I was full-tilt delusional.
我這輩子最害怕的一次
I have never in my life been as scared
就是那晚在那個林子里
as I was that night in the woods,
跪在地上
kit to the grit,
覺得自己死定了
fully believing my number's about to be called,
然后看見勇敢的生存者...
then seeing it happen to someone brave...
被殺了
to a survivor.
然后那種讓人嚇尿褲子的恐懼
And then the pants-pissing terror
看著那個場景一次又一次重現...
of the rinse and repeat of that very same event --
我...
I just...
我做不到
I couldn't.
來這邊意味著我再不用恐懼了
Being here means I'll never have to again.
假如你答應的話  你也不用了
And neither will you if you just say "yes."
求求你答應吧
Please say "yes."
他希望你能答應
He would want you to.
他不希望
He wouldn't.
我希望
I do.
我們依然活著
We're still here.
世道已經變了
Things have changed.
我們可以隨之做出改變  我們必須如此
We can change with 'em. We have to.
走吧
Go.
-他已經開始...  -拜托了
- He's, uh, starting to... - Please.
走吧
Go.
我還從沒見過你到晱~來呢
Don't think I've seen you outside the walls.
我建這些圍棷N是為了用的
Well, I built these walls to use them.
假如我想吃綠菜了  我可以吃沙拉
If I want greenery, I eat a salad.
那你為什么來這里
Then why are you here?
我本打算找你談談
I was hoping we could talk.
然后我看見你一個人跑出來
Then I saw you come out here alone.
我很擔心你
I was concerned.
你的朋友們呢
Where are your friends?
他們出去了
They went out.
他們在找需要的東西
They're looking for something they need.
你不去嗎
Without you?
我只是好奇  你怎么還留在這  瑪姬
Now, I'm just wondering -- Why you still here, Maggie?
卡森已經不在了
With Carson gone...
我聽說你要救他回來
I heard you were gonna get him back.
不是嗎
That not true?
還是只是說說而已
Was it just something you said?
瑪姬  你得信任我
Maggie, you've got to start trusting me.
人們都很緊張  很擔心
You know, people are tense, they're worried.
如果我們表現得像一伙
Everybody'd be a hell of a lot better
大家會安心得多
if we could present a-a united front.
如果我們能真正成為一伙  會輕松得多
It would be a lot easier if we actually were a united front.
你說得對
You're right.
我得對合作持更開放的態度
I need to be more open to working together.
我道歉
I apologize.
我從不希望我們之間鬧成這樣
I never intended for things between us to come to this point.
感謝你這么說
I appreciate that.
亡羊補牢永遠不晚  知道嗎
It's never too late to change. You know that?
如果你是認真的  我稍后會找你詳談
If you're serious, I'll come by later and we can talk more.
好
Fine.
太好了
Great.
我還以為很快就能完事
I thought this'd just take a second.
弄完之前  你能幫我留意一下四周嗎
Would you mind keeping an eye out while I finish up?
可以嗎
Could you do that?
樂意之至
Happy to.
來了一只
We got one.
我來
I'll do it.
我是來保護孕婦的
I'm here to protect the pregnant lady.
不用孕婦保護我
Don't need the pregnant lady to protect me.
你以前殺過行尸嗎
Have you ever killed one before?
沒殺過我就不可能站在這了
I wouldn't be here if I hadn't.
-沒事  我來吧  -不
- It's fine. I got it. - No.
天啊
Jesus.
好吧  你來
Fine. Do it.
瑪姬
Maggie!
救救我
Please help me!
你沒事吧
You okay?
他以前沒殺過行尸
He hasn't killed one before.
正在學習
He's learning.
他跟我們可不是這么說的
That's not what he told us.
謝謝你救我
Thanks for the help.
你自己抓到的嗎
You catch that yourself?
-那他媽當然  -?瑞秋
- Shit, yeah. - ?Rachel.
我是說  那當然
I mean, yeah.
-我去把它清理干凈  -好
- Gonna go clean it. - Okay.
別出聲
Stay quiet
手放頭上
and put your hands on your head.
在村里時我們就該殺了你
We should've just killed you in the village.
你會慶幸你們沒殺我的
You're gonna be glad you didn't.
你不是一個人來的  對吧
You're not alone, are you?
坐下
Sit.
你想干什么
What do you want?
我想讓你坐下
I want you to sit.
你好  辛蒂
Hey, Cyndie.
你保證過的
You promised.
對  我保證過
Yeah. I did.
把手放在頭上
Put your hands on your head.
我別無選擇
I didn't have a choice.
你來這干什么
Why are you here?
我說了  我別無選擇
I said I didn't have a choice.
但你們有  你倆都有
But you do, both of you do.
我的同伴現在就在外面
My friends are out there right now,
他們會攻占這里  希望不必開火
and they're gonna take this place, hopefully without firing a shot.
什么  你們要"攻占這里"
What? You're...you're gonna "Take this place"?
你在說什么
What are you talking about?
我們需要你們的槍
We need your guns.
什么
What?
我們要抵抗救世軍
We're gonna fight The Saviors.
-你們應該加入我們  -不
- You should join us. ?- No.
救世軍殺害了你們的父親
The Saviors killed your fathers,
兄弟  丈夫  兒子  而你們選擇逃避
your brothers, husbands, sons, and you ran from them.
我以為我們鏟除了他們
I thought we got rid of them.
碧翠絲說還有更多救世軍  她說得對
Beatrice said there was more out there, and she was right.
他們回來了
They came back.
殺了我的朋友們
They killed my friends.
殺了我的女友
They killed my girlfriend.
接管了我們  奪走了我們的一切
They took us over. They took everything from us.
我們對救世軍千依百順
We do whatever The Saviors tell us to do,
他們以為我們依然效忠  但不是
and they think we're still doing that, but we're not.
我們打算反抗
We're gonna fight them.
還有其他社區加入我們
And we have other communities beside us,
有了海邊旅館  我們就有了一支軍隊
and with Oceanside, we would have an army.
就這樣嗎
So, that's it?
"謝謝給槍  你們應該加入我們"
"Thanks for the guns. You should join us"?
如果我們聯手  可以打敗他們
If we fight them together, we can beat them.
我們必須試試
We have to try.
他們會贏的  塔拉  我見過  你也見過
They'll win, Tara. I've seen it. So have you.
和我們團隊的首領談談  瑞克
Just talk to the leader of my group, Rick.
只用談談  我們不必攻占這里
Just talk, and we don't have to take over this place.
我們不想那樣做
We don't want to.
我可以示意他們停下
I can give them the signal to stop this,
但是你必須現在就告訴我
but you have to tell me right now.
聽著  我們不只是藏在樹林里
Listen. We're not just hiding in the woods.
我們在做事  我們沒有放棄
We're doing something. We're not giving up.
我不想打破我的承諾  辛蒂
I didn't want to break my promise, Cyndie, okay?
但是世界可以屬于好人  公正的人
But the world can belong to good people, to fair people,
只要我們有足夠的勇氣去嘗試
if we're all just brave enough to try.
我們不是好人  也不勇敢
We are not good, and we are not brave.
你我都不是
Neither you nor me.
她是
She is.
所以我們才有現在這麻煩
That's why we're in this mess.
塔拉  如果你們拿走我們的槍
Look, Tara, if you take our guns,
還不如把我們全殺了
you might as well be killing us all.
這就是你們做的事
That's what you'll be doing.
我們應該和他們談談
We should talk to them.
不
No.
我們可以試著阻止這事
We can try to stop this.
不  辛蒂
No, Cyndie.
無所謂了
It doesn't matter.
沒法阻止了
You can't.
走
Go! Go!
武器庫
The arsenal!
趴下  快
On the ground. Now.
手抱頭
Those hands -- Put them on your head.
拜托
Please.
你的人殺我的人
Your people killing my people?
炸彈安置在晱~
The bombs were outside the walls.
你本可以阻止的
You could've stopped this.
我希望所有人都沒事  真的
Look, I hope everyone is okay. I do.
最好沒事
They better be.
起來
Stand up.
該走了
It's time to move.
我的腿
It's my legs.
站住  后退
Stop, stop. Back up. Back up.
辛蒂  別動
Cyndie, stop!
是空的  什么
It's empty. ?What?
沒裝彈
It's unloaded.
我們不是來傷人的
We didn't come here to hurt anybody.
辛蒂  給我
Cyndie, give it here.
快
Now.
娜塔尼亞  就和瑞克談談
Natania, just talk to Rick.
閉嘴
Shut up.
所有人蹲下
Everybody down!
手放頭上
Hands on your heads.
所有人冷靜
Everybody stay calm.
我們不想傷害任何人
We don't want anyone to get hurt.
別動  聽我們說
Stay down and listen to what we say.
我們想讓這件事盡量簡單和平地解決
We want this to go as simply and as peacefully as possible.
你們都可以做到
All of you can make it that way.
去那邊蹲著  安靜
Get down over there. Keep quiet.
我們搞出了很大動靜
Now, we made a lot of noise.
所以我們想盡快了事  這樣你們就可以派人
We want to wrap this up quick so you can send people
引開過來的行尸
to redirect anything coming this way.
塔拉說你們這片森林比較稀疏
Tara said your forests are relatively clear,
所以我們不會冒險
so we won't take any chances.
任何人都不必受傷
No one needs to get hurt.
重要的只是你們有什么  我們需要什么
This is just about what you have, what we need.
沒人可以帶走任何東西
Nobody's taking anything.
放了所有人
You need to let everyone go
立刻離開
and leave right now.
離開  不然她就得死
Just walk away or this one dies.
好  我們會離開
Yeah, we'll leave you alone.
但我們要帶走你們的武器
But we're taking your weapons with us.
這點不會改變
That's not gonna change.
你是娜塔尼亞  對嗎
It's Natania, right?
放下槍
Put the gun down,
我們來談談我們可以改變什么
and let's talk about what we can change.
不  馬上離開
No. Leave right now.
米恩瓊  不要
Michonne, don't!
我們只是不想被打擾
We just wanna be left alone.
沒問題  我們會離開
Yeah, we'll leave you alone.
立刻放開她
Just let go of her. Now.
不然我們就殺了你
Or we'll kill you.
我們都不想那樣
None of us want that.
他們想讓我們反抗救世軍
They want us to fight The Saviors.
我們試過  輸了  輸得很慘
We tried that. We lost. Too much.
我們不會再失去任何東西了
We're not gonna lose anymore --
不管是我們的槍  還是我們的安全
not our guns, not our safety,
我們做了那么多  好不容易才來這里
not after everything we've done to get here.
我們會贏的
We're gonna win --
只要有了你們的槍  無論你們幫不幫我們
with your guns, with or without your help.
娜塔尼亞  放下槍
Natania, put the gun down.
殺了我你也會死
You kill me, and you die.
我們的人一樣會拿走槍  什么都不會變
And my people take the guns and nothing changes.
也許我們應該試一下
Maybe we should try.
祖母  住手吧
Grandma, stop.
結束了
It's over.
和他們談談吧  好嗎
Just talk to them, okay?
還沒完
It's not over!
他們都忘了
They've forgotten.
你們都忘了
You've all forgotten.
你們中有些人真想反抗他們嗎
Some of you actually want to fight them?
經歷了那一切以后
After everything?
我們可以失去槍
We can lose our guns,
但我們也要離開這里去戰斗嗎
but us leaving this place to fight?
經歷了那么多事以后
After everything?
我必須提醒你們
I have to remind you!
是的
Yes.
我會這樣做  我會死
I am gonna do this, and then I'm gonna die.
但就是這么重要
But it's that important.
這是你們的人生  你們所有人的
This is your life, all of you.
想想它是什么樣的
Remember what it looks like.
想想他們以前是怎么對我們的
Remember what they did to us!
你們要看清楚  睜眼好好看著
You need to see this. Open your eyes!
瑞克  有行尸
Rick! Walkers!
所有人起來
Everybody up!
讓孩子們站到后面
Get the children behind us!
它們過來了
They're coming.
第一班  跟他們站一排
First shift, join them on the line.
拔刀  只殺行尸  只殺行尸
Knives out. Dead only. Dead only!
哪也別去
Don't go anywhere.
所有人  10英尺以內再開槍
Everyone, shots within 10 feet of the line.
就這樣
That's it.
開槍
Now!
不  我們不會跟你們一起反抗他們
No. We're not fighting them with you.
拿著你們的槍滾吧
So take your damn guns and go.
你贏了
You win.
不
No.
你贏了
You win.
叫點人來  清理干凈
Get some people in here. Clean this up.
怎么了
What?
你不會真的以為
You didn't actually think
我會讓你留著這把刀吧
I was gonna let you keep this, did you?
在我相信你效忠之前
You still got a ways to go
你還要走很長一段路
before I'll believe you're fully on board here.
一步步來嘛
Baby steps.
絕不是針對你
It is absolutely not personal.
如果情況調過來
If the situation was reversed,
你肯定也不會相信我
I'm sure you wouldn't believe me, either.
但是
Still...
你自救的方式
the way you saved yourself,
你剛向我投降的方式
the way you surrendered to me just now --
是個很好的開始
That is a damn good start.
但是  我們還得辦點事  薩沙
But we got to work on some things, Sasha.
不過我保證  我會盡量讓過程充滿樂趣
But I promise you, I will try to make it fun.
實話說了吧
Cards on the table...
一只小鳥告訴我
a little birdie told me
瑞克和你們其他的人在動歪腦筋
that Rick and the rest of your people are up to no good.
這需要改變
And, well, that needs to change,
而你要幫我改變
and you're gonna help me change it.
我們會找到一個雙贏的方法
We're gonna find us a win-win.
什么意思
How?
-你打算...  -我會給你找些東西
- What are you - Hey, I'm gonna get you some stuff
讓你更舒適
to make you more comfortable,
讓你體驗一下我們能提供什么
let you have a taste of what it is we have to offer.
好好享受一晚
Spend the night enjoying it,
因為明天
'cause tomorrow...
是個大日子
is gonna be a big day.
凱爾
Kal!
什么事
Yeah?
我需要你開車帶我去個地方
I'm gonna need you to drive me somewhere.
你最好打個包
You're gonna want to pack a bag.
在嗎
Hello?
我是尤金
It's Eugene.
聽說你愿意加入這里了
Word in the halls is that you're all-in with things here.
現在也許看起來不像
It may not seem like it now,
但我向你保證
but I assure you,
你同樣做了正確的選擇
you, too, made the correct select.
我錯了
I was wrong.
我做不到
I can't.
我不會做
I won't.
我一直坐在這里
I've been sitting here,
想著我怎么能做到
trying to figure out how I could,
發生了那么多事
with what happened,
我們的朋友們還在外面
with our friends still out there,
還被他們傷害著
still being hurt by them.
我不知道我怎么能那樣說
I don't know how I could've said that.
現在  我陷入了困境
And now...I am trapped.
你必須幫我
You have to help me.
我會的
I will.
我會幫你習慣現實
I'll help you get used to the idea
闡明利害  演示為什么...
and illustrate the equation and demonstrate why --
那是個錯誤
It was a mistake.
我本來準備好了
I was ready.
我知道如果我昨晚沒殺死他
I knew, if I didn't kill him last night,
我就完了
it'd be over.
我沒殺死他  所以就這樣吧
And I didn't, so it is.
必須這樣
It has to be.
你必須給我搞些東西來
You have to get me something --
刀  槍  剃須刀片
a knife, a gun, a razor blade.
為了尼根嗎
For Negan?
不
No!
不管怎樣  他都會利用我傷害我的朋友們
One way or another, he is gonna use me to hurt my friends --
我們的朋友們
our friends.
而我對此無能為力
And there is nothing I can do about it
除非我死了  不給他機會
except make sure I'm not alive to give him the chance.
只要我活著  他就會傷害他們
If he has me, he will hurt them.
我必須死
I have to die.
這是唯一的辦法
It's the only way.
我不認為...
I-I don't -- I-I don't think that --
我知道你不會做任何事阻止他們
I know you won't do anything to stop them.
我知道
I know that.
但是求你了  尤金
But, please, Eugene...
別讓他們利用我傷害我們的人
don't let them use me to hurt our people.
求你了  你必須給我一些東西了斷自己
Please, you have to give me something to stop this
槍  刀  玻璃
-- a gun, a knife, glass.
我不在乎
I don't care.
我必須死
I have to die.
求你了
Please.
我...
I...
我會考慮
I will consider it.
謝謝
Thank you.
我們不需要全拿走吧
We don't need all this, do we?
我們需要
Yeah. Yeah, we do.
不只是我殺的人
It's not just the ones I killed.
我也會想起我沒殺的人
I think about the people I didn't kill, too.
結束后我們會把槍送回來
We're gonna bring them back when it's all over.
我想跟你們走
I-I want to go with you.
我們有些人想反抗  但不是所有人
Some of us do, but not all of us,
必須達成共識她們才加入
and it has to be all of us.
我祖母認為你們都會死
My grandmother thinks you'll all be dead.
你祖母很多想法都是錯的
Yeah, well, your grandmother's wrong about a lot of things.
她人呢
Where is she?
她不想看見這個
She didn't want to see this.
她躺下了  我把她打得挺重
She's lying down. I hit her pretty hard.
感謝你之前救我命
Thanks for saving my life before.
還有另一次
And the other time.
Oh, and then the other time.
也許還有今天
?Maybe today.
謝謝
Thanks.
Thank you.
你所做的事
For what you're doing.
不給我們留一把嗎
You're not leaving us any?
不留  回見  瑞秋
Nope. See ya later, Rachel.
你還好吧
You okay?
還好
Yeah.
你說得對
You're right.
我不必內疚
I don't have to feel bad.
薩沙
Sasha?
我在
I'm here.
我仔細考慮權衡了上次談話
I've given our last exchange a good, hard pro/con think.
我決定滿足你的請求
I've decided to grant your request.
用這個就行
This will do it.
這是毒藥  本人親手制作
It's a poison, homemade by yours truly.
攝入后約20至30分鐘內必死
It will bring about certain death in approximately 20 to 30 minutes upon the moment of ingestion.
我相信應該是無痛的
I would like to believe that it's painless.
我不太確定
I am not -- I'm not certain.
我做藥是因為曾有人提過類似請求
I made it at the behest of others for similar reasons,
后來我發現她們給了我虛假信息
only it came to pass that they were feeding me the bum's steer,
于是我懸崖勒馬
so I cut bait.
現在的不同之處是
The difference here is that
我們倆是長期旅伴
you and I have been long-time traveling companions,
你證明了自己是一個誠實勇敢
and you have proven yourself to be honest, brave,
具備完全自我意識的人
and fully self-aware.
我確信我欠你人情
I'm certain I owe you for things.
你讓我幫你找解脫辦法
You asked me for a way out.
我找到了一個
I had access to one.
首先聲明  我完全不希望你死
For the record, I absolutely do not want you to go.
但是聽起來你已經下了必死之心
But it sounds to me like you happen to be already gone.
你沒事吧
Hey, are you okay?
薩沙在哪
Where's Sasha?
有人來了
There's someone here.
慢點  等等
Slow down. Come on. Whoa!
他說他想幫我們
He says he wants to help us.
是真的嗎
That true?
你想幫忙
You want to help?
是的
I do.
好
Okay.
跪下
Get on your knees.